A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller personal papers, AIA-IBEC, Series B FA339
Rockefeller Archive Center
- IBEN Co., 1956-1958 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  To package and market soluble coffee in Europe; an affiliate of IBEC; IBEC interest sold to Tenco. Correspondents include NAR, Berent Friele.
- IBEC (International Basic Economy Corporation) - Ireland, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  Digest of IBEC Technical Services Corporation (ITSC). Survey of Ireland's industrial potentials. Correspondents include Stacy May.
- IBEC - Italian [Islands] Interests, 1956-1957 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  Reports on Italian economic conditions. Possible NAR commitments in Italy. Correspondents include NAR, R. Mattioli.
- IBEC - Investment Committee, 1956-1958 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  Reports on investments. Agendas of committee meetings. Activities in Latin America, Europe, and Asia.
- IBEC - Technical Services Corp. (ITSC), 1947-1953 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  Robert Moses report on Brazil lands. Report on Trans-Arabian Highway. Corporation liquidated in 1953. 1948 report on Cuba for the Chase Bank by Stacy May. Correspondents include NAR, W. K. Harrison, George Dudley.
- IBEC Technical Services Corporation - Caracas La Guira Highway, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 41)
- IBEC Technical Services Corporation - Finances, 1951-1953 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  Purchase and sale of securities.
- AIA - International Development Services, Inc. (IDS), 1953 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  AIA grant to IDS. Correspondents include NAR, Robert W. Hudgens.
- AIA - Economic Development in Cuba, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 44)
- AIA IRI (IBEC Research Institute) Merger, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  Arrangements for merger. Correspondents include NAR, Lawrence Levy.
- IBEC Research Institute - Reports - Stacy May Ecuador Study, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 46)
- IBEC Research Institute - Reports - IBEC Research Institute Description, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 47)
- IBEC Research Institute - Reports - Venezuelan Studies, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 48)
- IBEC Research Institute - Reports - Brazil Progress Report, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 49)
- IBEC Research Institute - Reports - Brazil Coffee Program, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 50)
- IBEC Research Institute - Reports - Corn Pre-Emergence Weed Control, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 51)
- IBEC Research Institute - Reports - Venezuelan Herbicide Program, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 52)
- IBEC Research Institute - Reports - Possible Increase in Scope of Activities, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 53)
- IBEC Research Institute - Reports - Summary of Brazil Projects, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 54)
- IBEC Research Institute - Reports - Brazil Progress Report, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 55)
- IBEC Research Institute - Reports - Coffee Studies and Reports, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 56)
- IBEC Research Institute - Reports - Cereals Investigations, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 57)
- IBEC Research Institute - Reports - Research in Brazil, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 58)
- IBEC Research Institute - Brazil - Progress Reports, 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 59)
- IBEC Research Institute - Brazil - Progress Reports, 1956-1957 (Box 7, Folder 60)
- IBEC Research Institute - Brazil - Progress Reports, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 61)
- IBEC Research Institute - Agricultural, Chemical and Related Subjects, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 62)
- IBEC Research Institute - Coffee Research in Brazil, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 63)
- Kulka Electric Manufacturing Co., 1956 (Box 7, Folder 64)
  Investigating company before possible purchase by IBEC. No consummation here.
- Latin American Cooperatives - T. B. Keehan Report, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 65)
  A draft report on cooperatives. Proposes AIA participation in cooperative program. Correspondents include T. B. Keehan.
- Luncheon Meeting Minutes, February 1959 (Box 7, Folder 66)
  Policy decision regarding IBEC made at meetings January-February 1959. Buying and selling of interests in various companies and activities.
- Mexico - Investment Bank, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 67)
  1953 Chase Bank study of investment possibilities in Mexico.
- [MIDEC] Middle East Industrial Development, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 68)
  Organization of MIDEC. No substance here. Correspondents include NAR.
- Oreamuno, J. R., 1949-1950 (Box 7, Folder 69)
  Reports on Venezuelan affairs. Oreamuno's plans to become Costa Rican ambassador to Washington. Correspondents include NAR, J. Oreamuno.
- PACA (Productora Agro Pecuaria, Compania Anomina), 1947-1951 (Box 7, Folder 70)
  Venezuelan farm operations in corn and rice. Correspondents include NAR, John E. Lockwood.
- PACA (Productora Agro Pecuaria, Compania Anomina) - Camacho Property Central Bolivar, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 71)
- AIA - Peru, 1951-1955 (Box 7, Folder 72)
  John Camp for nutrition, education programs in Peru. Plans for development of Cuzco. Correspondents include John Camp, NAR, R. Hudgens.
- Plax do Brasil, 1951-1954 (Box 7, Folder 73)
  IBEC Brazilian plastic project. No progress. Correspondents include NAR.
- Productos de Cafe - El Salvador, 1954-1958 (Box 7, Folder 74)
  IBEC coffee operations in El Salvador. Soluble coffee. IBEC owned 30%. Correspondents include NAR.
- Russell, R. P., 1947-1964 (Box 8, Folder 75)
  Went to Caracas in 1947. Direct reports to NAR on conditions in field and office. Trips to other Latin American locations. Confidential reports to NAR. Correspondents include NAR, R. P. Russell.
- Sementes Agroceres, S. A. (SASA), 1952-1956 (Box 8, Folder 76)
  Corn producing reports. Correspondents include NAR.
- Supermarkets - Brazil - Shopping Center, 1956-1957 (Box 8, Folder 77)
  IBEC project in Sao Paulo. Cost of land. Decision not to go ahead. Correspondents include NAR, W. B. Stroud.
- Supermarkets - Panama, 1956-1957 (Box 8, Folder 78)
  IBEC project. Planning stages. Political complications. Decision against going into business. Correspondents include NAR, John French.
- Supermarkets - Peru - Shopping Center, 1954-1957 (Box 8, Folder 79)
  Proposal for supermarket in Lima. Planning. Operation by IBEC. Milk. Slow increase in sales. Shopping center operation. Correspondents include NAR, Lawrence Levy, Bernardo Jofre.
- Supermarkets - Puerto Rico, Cuba, 1955-1958 (Box 8, Folder 80)
  Planning operation. Possible competition. Possible Cuban operation. Difficulties in operation. Correspondents include NAR, W. S. Bradford.
- Supermarkets - Venezuela, 1956-1961 (Box 8, Folder 81)
  Organization. Competition. Share of market. Consolidation of operations. Correspondents include NAR, B. Gofer.
- Stroud, W. B. D., resigned, 1957-1964 (Box 8, Folder 82)
  Reports of IBEC activity. Argentine Oil. Resignation 1964. Correspondents include NAR, W. B. D. Stroud.
- Tenco (Coffee), 1955-1960 (Box 8, Folder 83)
  Instant coffee producers in Linden, New Jersey. Sale to Minute Maid organization. Plans for coffee growing production of soluble coffee in El Salvador. Formation of Tenco. Expansion in Mexico, Brazil, and Africa. Sales and production problems. Salvador research. Financial, accounting statements. Correspondents include NAR, Berent Friele, Ed Aborn.
- Toro, A. Jr., 1947-1957 (Box 8, Folder 84)
  Participation in CADA (Compania Anomina Distribuidora de Alimentos). Relations with VBEC merchandising division. Problems. Left organization. Correspondents include NAR, A. Toro, Berent Friele.
- [Transoceanic] American Overseas Investing (Finance) Co. Inc., 1954-1959 (Box 9, Folder 85)
  Organized 1955 to finance export shipments. IBEC investment in 1957. Negotiations to purchase. Expansion into medium term development loans. Correspondents include NAR, N. A. Bogdan.
- AIA - Treasurer - N. Y. General, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 86)
  Staff memoranda distributing policy decisions to staff. Policy committee meeting minutes.
- AIA - Venezuela, 1947-1959 (Box 9, Folder 87)
  Preliminary planning. Maddox report on 1949 conditions, 1950 review of program. Reports on program progress. Expansion of program. Changes in program. Mass communications program. Correspondents include NAR, W. R. Hudgens, John Camp.
- AIA - Venezuela - Labor Unions, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 88)
  Discussion of company unions. U.S. opposition to company unions in Venezuela.
- AIA - Venezuela - NAR Visit to Betancourt - NAR Notes, Memos, etc., 1947 (Box 9, Folder 89)
  Disagreement between AIA and Venezuela government on AIA operations. Misunderstanding. NAR preparation of material to present to Betancourt. Detail of trip. Success of mission. Memoranda and statements on purpose of AIA. Correspondents include NAR, John E. Lockwood, Francis A. Jamieson, President Betancourt.
- AIA - Venezuela - NAR Visit to Betancourt - Material NAR took to Venezuela, June 1947 (Box 9, Folder 90)
- AIA - Venezuela - NAR Visit to Betancourt - Extra Copies of Report, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 91)
- VBEC (Venezuelan Basic Economy Corporation), 1947-1954 (Box 10, Folder 92)
  VBEC (Venezuelan Basic Economy Corporation) financial condition. Relations with oil companies. Policy changes. Correspondents include NAR, L. Levy.
- VEFISA, 1957-1958 (Box 10, Folder 93)
  IBEC Venezuelan finance company. To finance import trucks and cars. Correspondents include NAR.
- AIA - Printed Reports - 1947 Report on Compania Agricola Industrial de Bocaina (Box 10, Folder 94)
- AIA - Printed Reports - [French Jones Report] Appraisal of Major Programs: AIA in Venezuela, 1951 (Box 10, Folder 95)
- AIA - Printed Reports - CBR (Council of Rural Development) Venezuelan Agriculture, 1952 (Box 10, Folder 96)
- AIA - Printed Reports - Prospectus on Compania Anomina Lactuaria del Caribe (CALCA), 1944-1947 (Box 10, Folder 97)
- AIA - Printed Reports - Inter-American Popular Information Program (PIIP), 1957 (Box 10, Folder 98)
- AIA - Printed Reports - Plan for Industrial Education Valencia, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 99)
- AIA - Printed Reports - 5V Sound Atom Report, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 100)
- AIA - Printed Reports - 1964 Report on Rural Youth Club Programs (Box 10, Folder 101)
- AIA - Administration Memos, 1947 (Box 10, Folder 102)
  Report policies, purchasing procedures, personnel office procedure, general organization. Correspondents include John Camp.
- IBEC - Administration Memos, 1947 (Box 10, Folder 103)
  Cables, personnel, holidays, organization, project procedure, purchasing, public relations, reports, files. Correspondents include W. H. Alton.
- AIA - Organization and Financial, 1946-1947 (Box 11, Folder 104)
  NAR to John Davison Rockefeller Jr. memo, 1946 on purposes. 1947 projects. Staff. Correspondents include NAR.
- IBEC-AIA - Agreements, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 105)
  Policy covering inter-agency agreements.
- IBEC - Babassee Nuts, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 106)
  Investigation of economic potential of babassee nuts. No follow through. Correspondents include NAR, Stacy May.
- IBEC - Bassert Process, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 107)
  Process for hydrogen reduction of iron ore. Studies by Rockefeller Brothers Inc. VBEC (Venezuelan Basic Economy Corporation) interested in development of process with Venezuelan firm. Detail negotiations. Pilot for plans. Agreement. Correspondents include NAR, H. O. Castillo, R. P. Russell.
- AIA-IBEC Board Meetings, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 108)
  Agendas, minutes and memoranda prepared for board meetings.
- IBEC - Cargill, Inc., 1947 (Box 11, Folder 109)
  Grain production in Venezuela and Brazil; building silos for storage. Cargill agrees to study problem and make recommendations. Their report and proposal. Prospects for cooperation. Correspondents include NAR, Berent Friele, Stacy May, John Camp.
- IBEC - Dry Ice, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 110)
  Investigation of Mexican system of manufacturing dry ice. Production of dry ice in Venezuela. NAR investment purchased by IBEC. Correspondents include NAR, J. R. Oreamuno.
- IBEC - Frozen Foods, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 111)
  Conference with Birdseye people on potential market. Survey of Caracas outlets for frozen foods. Connection with fish company. Correspondents include John Camp, NAR, W. D. Bradford.
- AIA - Brazil - Displaced Persons Colonization, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 112)
  Possible project to assist immigration into Brazil. Decision not to participate. Correspondents include NAR, K. J. Kadow, Berent Friele.
- IBEC - AIA - Oil Company Participation, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 113)
  Agreement by Creole, Socony, Esso and Shell to participate in AIA program in Venezuela. Description of purposes and work to oil companies. Development of prospectus. Oil company comments on IBEC business methods. Correspondents include NAR, J. N. Loudon, G. W. Hamilton, Brewster Jennings, John Camp.
- IBEC - Finance, 1947 (Box 12, Folder 114)
  Capital structure. Recapitulation. Annuity plans. Comments in balance sheets. Investment policies. Correspondents include NAR, J. W. Hisle, T. S. Gates.
- AIA IBEC - Executive Committee Meetings, 1947 (Box 12, Folder 115)
  Minutes of meetings.
- AIA IBEC - Policy Committee Minutes, 1947 (Box 12, Folder 116)
  Minutes of meetings of AIA and IBEC.
- AIA IBEC - Staff Committee Meetings, 1947 (Box 12, Folder 117)
  Minutes of meetings planning daily operations of AIA and IBEC. Correspondents include NAR.
- IBEC - Brazil - Agriculture Servicing Organization, 1947 (Box 12, Folder 118)
  Negotiations with International Harvester and Ferguson on tractors. Discussion of objectives and methods. Correspondents include NAR, Berent Friele, Stacy May, L. C. Heilbronner.
- IBEC - Brazil - Cocoa Project, 1947 (Box 12, Folder 119)
  Study of cocoa production possibilities in Brazil. Correspondents include Stacy May.
- IBEC - Brazil - Financial and Legal, 1947 (Box 12, Folder 120)
  Establishing organization in Brazil. Budgets. John Davison Rockefeller 3rd investment in IBEC. Correspondents include D. Jackson.
- IBEC - Brazil - Fomento Agro - Pecuario, S.A., 1947 (Box 12, Folder 121)
  To raise hogs in small economically balanced units. Planning, selection of a manager. Distribution of stock. Setting up farms. Initial success. Correspondents include NAR, T. Q. Barbosa, J. B. Griffing.
- IBEC - Brazil - Organization, 1947 (Box 12, Folder 122)
  Kadow outline of proposed work. Developing program. Staff changes. Correspondents include D. W. Jackson, K. J. Kadow, NAR, Stacy May.
- IBEC - Brazil - Program, 1947 (Box 12, Folder 123)
  Stacy May's report on possibilities in Brazil. Joseph Jennan's report on the Development of New Areas. Correspondents include NAR, Stacy May, Joe Jennan.
- IBEC - Brazil - Progress Reports, 1947 (Box 12, Folder 124)
  Kadow reports on field progress. Reports sent to New York semi-monthly. Correspondents include NAR, K. J. Kadow, D. W. Jackson.
- IBEC - Brazil - Staff Meetings, 1947 (Box 12, Folder 125)
  Minutes of meetings of staff in Rio de Janeiro. Discussion of program.
- IBEC - Brazil - Sementes Agroceros, S.A., 1947 (Box 12, Folder 126)
  Hybrid corn seed company. Organization, operation, inspections. Rockefeller Foundation. Correspondents include NAR, D. W. Jackson.
- IBEC - Brazil - Serra da Bocaina Project, 1947 (Box 12, Folder 127)
  Large scale lumber scheme. Investigation of possible lumber industry partners. Assembling of lands. Collapse of project. Correspondents include K. J. Kadow, NAR, John E. Lockwood.
- IBEC - Brazil - Sul [South] America Transportes e Commercio, 1947 (Box 13, Folder 128)
  Trucking operation between Santos and Sao Paulo. Misunderstandings. Correspondents include NAR, K. J. Kadow, Forrest W. Manker.
- IBEC - Technical Services Inc. (ITSC), 1947 (Box 13, Folder 129)
  Separate organization to conduct surveys and engineering studies and to manage financing and construction. Emphasis on transportation. Organization. Possible projects. Correspondents include NAR, Wally K. Harrison, Berent Friele.
- IBEC Technical Services Corporation - La Guaira Port Survey, 1947 (Box 13, Folder 130)
  Assembly project task force. Purposes of study. Arrangements for task force. Correspondents include NAR, W. K. Harrison.
- IBEC Technical Services Corporation - Sao Paulo Airport Survey, 1947 (Box 13, Folder 131)
  To formulate proposal to state of Sao Paulo for new airport. Task force. Confusion of terms of contract. Correspondents include NAR, W. K. Harrison.
- IBEC Technical Services Corporation - Slaughter House, 1947 (Box 13, Folder 132)
  Proposal for technical assistance to government. Related cattle slaughtering. Correspondents include NAR, John Camp.
- IBEC Technical Services Corporation - Surveys, 1947 (Box 13, Folder 133)
  Shoe industry, textiles, transit surveys, progress reports. Correspondents include NAR, J. R. Oreamuno.
- AIA - Brazil - [Fertility Experiments] Fertilizer, 1947 (Box 13, Folder 134)
  Efforts to import phosphate fertilizers into Brazil. Proposed fertilizer experiment. Correspondents include NAR, D. W. Jackson.
- AIA - Brazil - Nutrition, 1947 (Box 13, Folder 135)
  Plans for nutrition and home demonstration program. Bringing Brazilians to the U.S. for training. corn products company participation. Correspondents include K. J. Kadow, D. Jackson.
- AIA - Brazil - Progress Reports, 1947 (Box 13, Folder 136)
  Semi-monthly reports from Rio office, July-December 1947.
- AIA - Venezuela, 1947 (Box 13, Folder 137)
  Plans for balancing VBEC (Venezuelan Basic Economy Corporation) activities in Venezuela with an AIA program. Developing proposals in information, training, and education. Turrialba project. Correspondents include John R. Camp, K. J. Kadow.
- VBEC (Venezuelan Basic Economy Corporation) - Advisory Committee File, 1947 (Box 13, Folder 138)
  Effort to create committee of eminent Venezuelans to make suggestions on VBEC (Venezuelan Basic Economy Corporation) program. Committee formed. No action here. Correspondents include NAR, W. F. Coles.
- VBEC (Venezuelan Basic Economy Corporation) - Compania Anonima Lactuaria del Caribe (CALCA), 1947 (Box 14, Folder 139)
  Study of possible reconstituted milk program in Caracas. Shift from AIA to IBEC project. Organization of company with Golden State Company. Correspondents include M. Tucker, NAr, M. W. Abby.
- VBEC (Venezuelan Basic Economy Corporation) - Compania Anonima Distribuidora de Alimintos (CADA), 1947 (Box 14, Folder 140)
  Selection of A. B. Toro as General Manager of food distribution project. Stacy May memo. Cooperation with oil companies. Organization of operations. Correspondents include NAR, Stacy May, A. B. Toro, John R. Camp.
- VBEC (Venezuelan Basic Economy Corporation) - Financial, Legal and Organization, 1947 (Box 14, Folder 141)
  Incorporation and capital structure detail. Transfer of funds. Stock holders rights. Budgets. Staff arrangements and responsibilities. Correspondents include NAR, John E. Lockwood, John Camp, J. W. Hisle, R. P. Russell.
- VBEC (Venezuelan Basic Economy Corporation) - Government Correspondence, 1947 (Box 14, Folder 142)
  NAR with Romulo Betencourt about purposes of VBEC (Venezuelan Basic Economy Corporation). Correspondents include NAR, R. Betancourt.
- VBEC (Venezuelan Basic Economy Corporation) - Public Relations, 1947 (Box 14, Folder 143)
  Policy development in field of public relations. Some releases. Correspondents include Frank Jamieson, NAR.
- VBEC (Venezuelan Basic Economy Corporation) - Project Progress, 1947 (Box 14, Folder 144)
  Preliminary project planning. Progress of project, policy changes, air transportation, housing, immigration and others. Correspondents include K. J. Kadow, NAR, John Camp, Stacy May.
- VBEC (Venezuelan Basic Economy Corporation) - Compania Anonima de Peca y Productos Congelados, 1947 (Box 14, Folder 145)
  Study of fish market possibilities. Frozen food combination. Emerging fish program. Correspondents include NAR, Stacy May, Frances W. Taylor.
- Productora Agro-Pecuaria, Compania Anonima (PACA, CAPA), 1947 (Box 15, Folder 146)
  Efforts to reduce food prices in Venezuela. Cooperation with oil companies. Plan to buy and use land for food production and for experimental work. Correspondents include Stacy May, NAR, W. D. Bradford.
- Productora Agro-Pecuaria, Compania Anonima (PACA, CAPA) - Projects, 1947 (Box 15, Folder 147)
  Livestock, rice, vegetables, fertilizer, Central Bolivia farm projects to implement efforts to reduce unit cost of Venezuelan food. Correspondents include NAR, John R. Camp, W. D. Bradford.
- VBEC (Venezuelan Basic Economy Corporation) - Compania Anonima Hotelera, 1947 (Box 15, Folder 148)
  Negotiations on possible sale of Hotel Avila to Webb and Knapp. Correspondents include NAR.
- AIA-IBEC Certificates, By-Laws, Summary Statements, 1952-1957 (Box 15, Folder 149)
  Copies of some certificates of incorporation, prepared summaries of corporate structure.
- Memorandum on IBEC Securities Corporation, 1948 (Box 15, Folder 150)
- Investment Bank in Brazil - IBEC Chase Bank, 1951 (Box 15, Folder 151)
- Appraisal, Gould Paper Company, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 152)
- VBEC (Venezuelan Basic Economy Corporation) and Affiliated Companies - Progress Reports, 1949 (Box 15, Folder 153)
- AIA-IBEC - Project Proposal, CADA (Compania Anomina Distribuidora de Alimentos), 1947 (Box 16, Folder 154)
- AIA-IBEC - Project Proposal, Compania Anonima Lactuaria del Caribe (CALCA), 1947 (Box 16, Folder 155)
- AIA-IBEC - Project Proposal, CAPCO, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 156)
- IBEC - Crebbs, Chester M., 1955-1957 (Box 16, Folder 157)
- IBEC - Oil Projects - Crebbs, Chester M., 1951-1956 (Box 16, Folder 158)
- IBEC - Oil Royalties - Crebbs, Chester M., 1954, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 159)
- IBEC - Avila Oil Company Financial Statements, 1954, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 160)
- IBEC - Oil and Gas Program, Carl E. Siegesmund, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 161)
- IBEC - Oil and Gas Program, Carl E. Siegesmund, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 162)
- IBEC - Appraisal Property, Crebbs, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 163)
- IBEC - Oil Avila Co., 1952-1957 (Box 17, Folder 164)
- IBEC - Oil Projects, 1951-1959 (Box 17, Folder 165)
- IBEC - Oil Projects - Co-Owners, Interest Sold, May 1957 (Box 17, Folder 166)
- IBEC - Oil Projects - H. J. Mosser- Pecos County, Texas, 1951-1952 (Box 17, Folder 167)
- IBEC - Oil Projects - Weymouth, George T., 1952 (Box 17, Folder 168)
- IBEC - Oil Royalties, 1952-1956 (Box 17, Folder 169)
- IBEC - Oil File - C. M. Crebbs, 1955-1956 (Box 17, Folder 170)
- IBEC - Oil Investment - Crebbs' - Finance/Accounting, 1954-1956 (Box 17, Folder 171)
- IBEC - Oil Investment - Crebbs' - Finance/Accounting, Well Report, 1954-1956 (Box 17, Folder 172)
- IBEC - Oil Investment - Crebbs' - General, 1954-1956 (Box 17, Folder 173)
- IBEC - Oil EB Reports - Crebbs', 1954-1956 (Box 17, Folder 174)
- IBEC - Oil Investment - Crebbs' - Legal, 1954-1956 (Box 17, Folder 175)
- IBEC - Oil Investment - Crebbs' - Organization Office Procedure, 1954 (Box 17, Folder 176)
- IBEC - Oil Investment - Crebbs' - Weekly Report Well Progress, 1955-1956 (Box 18, Folder 177)
- IBEC - Oil Investment - Crebbs' - Atascosa County, Texas - Northwest Imogene, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 178)
- IBEC - Oil Investment - Crebbs' - Bee County, Texas - South Mineral Prospect, 1954-1956 (Box 18, Folder 179)
- IBEC - Oil Investment - Crebbs' - Brooks County, Texas - South Gyp Hill Area, 1955-1956 (Box 18, Folder 180)
- IBEC - Oil Investment - Crebbs' - Central Crockett County, Texas - Shannon Area, 1954-1956 (Box 18, Folder 181)
- IBEC - Oil Investment - Crebbs' - Finance/Accounting - Chambers County, Texas - Cedar Bayou Area, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 182)
- IBEC - Oil Investment - Crebbs' - Legal - Chambers County, Texas, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 183)
- IBEC - Oil Investment - Crebbs' - Operations - Chambers County, Texas, Williams #1, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 184)
- IBEC - Oil Investment - Crebbs' - SE7 Sisters Project - Duval County, Texas, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 185)
- IBEC - Oil Investment - Crebbs' - Legal - Elbert County, Colorado - Kiowa Area, 1954-1956 (Box 18, Folder 186)
- IBEC - Oil Investment - Crebbs' - Operations - Elbert County, Colorado - Kiowa Area, 1954-1956 (Box 18, Folder 187)
- IBEC - Oil Investment - Crebbs' - El Paso County, Colorado - Big Springs, Dome Area, 1954-1956 (Box 18, Folder 188)
- IBEC - Oil Investment - Crebbs' - Garza County, Texas - G. W. Connell #1, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 189)